Cayce Family Collection
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
Cayce Family Collection
1855 2013
Coll. 1
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
38 Linear Feet
Cayce, Edgar
Cayce, Gertrude Evans
Cayce, Hugh Lynn
Cayce, Edgar Evans
Cayce, Charles Thomas
Arrangement
Arranged in 4 series: 1. Cayce Family, 1855-2013. 2. Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1907-1982. 3. Edgar Evans Cayce, 1950-2013. 4. Charles Thomas Cayce, 1984-1990.
The Hugh Lynn Cayce series is based upon the arrangement created by Norrene Leary, former secretary to Hugh Lynn Cayce.
Biographical / Historical
The Cayce Family of Hopkinsville, Ky., included Edgar Cayce (1877-1945), known as the "sleeping prophet," the "father of holistic medicine," and the most documented psychic of the 20th century; his wife, Gertrude Evans Cayce (1880-1945), who supported her husband's work and served as the conductor for his readings; Edgar Cayce's father, Leslie Burr Cayce (1853-1937); and the children of Edgar and Gertrude, Hugh Lynn (1907-1982), manager of the Association for Research and Enlightenment, established in 1931, and Edgar Evans (1918-2013), electrical engineer and author.
Scope and Contents
The collection is primarily composed of paper materials, including correspondence, legal papers, and publications. Other materials include artifacts, certificates, news clippings, photographs, and audio-visual materials. The Hugh Lynn Cayce series comprises the majority of the collection.
- Edgar and Gertrude Cayce, 1897 2014
  - Box 1
    - biographical sketches [Edgar Cayce, 1936 1941; Folder 1:1
    - biographical sketch [Edgar Cayce's Memoirs 1877-1924 as dictated by Gladys Davis Turner], Folder 1:2
    - booklet [Fillmore's Concert Quarterly for Sunday Schools], 1897; Folder 1:3
    - correspondence [Edgar Cayce and David E. Kahn], 1923; Folder 1:4
    - correspondence [Edgar Cayce and Madison Wyrick; Mrs. H.S. Evans; Lydia Schrader Gray; Lorraine Schrader; Norfolk Study Group], 1923 1944; Folder 1:5
    - correspondence [Edgar Cayce and Claude A. Rice], 1935; Folder 1:6
    - court case [Edgar Cayce v. A.D. Noe], 1912 1913; Folder 1:7
    - crossword puzzles, 1931; Folder 1:8
    - golf score record [Edgar Cayce], 1936; Folder 1:9
    - photograph [Jeanne LeNoir], 1939 1940; Folder 1:10
    - photograph [Verna Elizabeth Piersen], 1916 1917; Folder 1:11
    - correspondence [personal]; Gertrude Cayce, 1906 1907; Folder 1:12
    - financial materials [Edgar and Gertrude Cayce] [, 1907 1945; Folder 1:13
    - magazine [Life], June 4, 1909; Folder 1:14
    - newsclippings [Edgar and Gertrude Cayce], 1897 1979; Folder 1:15
    - newsclippings [Edgar Cayce Psychic Diagnostician], 1910 1911; Folder 1:16
    - pamphlets [Edgar Cayce biographical information], 1964 1972; Folder 1:17
    - reports [Cayce Institute of Psychic Research], 1923 1924; Folder 1:18
    - writing contest publications, 1928; Folder 1:19
  - Box 2
    - Cayce family, correspondence [genealogy], 1922 1986; Folder 2:1
    - Cayce family, family reunion materials, 1988 1997; Folder 2:2
    - Cayce family, genealogical outlines [Cayce, Garrett, Major, Salter, Sands], 1994 2011; Folder 2:3
    - Cayce family, genealogical outline [The Descendants of Thomas Jefferson Cayce and Sarah Pearline Thomas], 2014; Folder 2:4
  - Box 3
    - articles of incorporation [Cayce Petroleum], 1921 1922; Folder 3:1
    - contract [Culpeper et. al.], 1921; Folder 3:2
    - contract [Live Oak Oil Association and Cayce Petroleum Company], 1921; Folder 3:3
    - contract [Cayce Petroleum Company and L.W. Martin and Company], 1921; Folder 3:4
    - contract [Miami Farms Company], 1921; Folder 3:5
    - contracts [Edgar Cayce and Moore family, Lillie B. Pitts, Charles and Mattie Taff], 1918 1921; Folder 3:6
    - contract [Tex Rice], 1922; Folder 3:7
    - contract [C.W. Tidwell, Basque County Texas Trustee; L.W. Martin and Company], 1921; Folder 3:8
    - contract [trust estate; W.J. Moore, Louise Moore], 1922; Folder 3:9
    - contract [C.S. Willmott], 1923; Folder 3:10
    - contract [C.S. Willmott, E.A. Hawley, J.S. Moore, J.S. Rutherford], 1924; Folder 3:11
    - correspondence [Cayce Petroleum], 1918 1967; Folder 3:12-3:15
    - declaration of trust [Cayce Petroleum], 1921; Folder 3:16
    - correspondence [T.J. McReynolds], 1921; Folder 3:17
    - financial records [Cayce Petroleum], 1921 1923; Folder 3:18
    - geological reports [Central Texas], 1919 1921; Folder 3:19
    - lease assignment of fractional interest [Arthur Lammers, Edgar Cayce], 1923; Folder 3:20
    - leases [Live Oak Oil and Gas Association], 1910 1921; Folder 3:21-3:22
    - memorandum of agreement [Edgar Cayce, Telegram Oil Company], 1923; Folder 3:23
    - memorandum of agreement [Edgar Cayce, Madison Wyrick, Telegram Oil Company], 1923; Folder 3:24
    - minutes [Cayce Petroleum], 1921 1922; Folder 3:25
    - pamphlet [Hilburn Oil and Royalty Company], 1920 1925; Folder 3:26
    - pooling agreement [Edgar Cayce, trustee; Unit Holders in the Cayce Petroleum Company], 1921; Folder 3:27
    - stock certificate [Cayce Petroleum Company], 1920; Folder 3:28
    - writing, undated; Folder 3:29
    - suggestion books [Gertrude Cayce], undated; Folder 3:30
  - Box 3A
    - correspondence [Hereward Carrington], 1933 1935; Folder 3A:1
    - correspondence [Sarah Cayce Hesson], 1942 1944; Folder 3A:2
    - correspondence [Elsie Sechrist], 1943 1944; Folder 3A:3
    - lectures [Edgar Cayce], 1930 1939; Folder 3A:4
    - manuscript [Edgar Cayce's Memoirs], 1932 1938; Folder 3A:5-3A:6
- Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1907 1982
  - Archaeology, 1966 1997
    - Box 4
      - contract [Edgar Cayce Foundation and Laserium Orange] Egypt Project, 1978; Folder 4:1
      - correspondence [Carolyn Amundson], 1980 1982; Folder 4:2
      - correspondence [Archaeological Institute of America], 1967 1968; Folder 4:3
      - correspondence [Archaeology] Bimini, 1971 1980; Folder 4:4
      - correspondence [archaeology students], 1979 1982; Folder 4:5
      - correspondence [Charles Thomas Cayce] Egypt Project, 1974 1977; Folder 4:6
      - correspondence [Edgar Evans Cayce] Egypt Project, 1977; Folder 4:7
      - correspondence [Gail Cayce] Egypt Project, 1976 1979; Folder 4:8
      - correspondence [archaeology] intuitive, 1974 1979; Folder 4:9
      - correspondence [archaeology] outside organizations, 1972 1977; Folder 4:10-4:12
      - correspondence [E.C.F. Trustees], 1978 1979; Folder 4:13
      - correspondence [Egypt Project], 1975 1982; Folder 4:14-4:16
      - correspondence [Egypt Project board reports], 1977 1978; Folder 4:17
    - Box 5
      - correspondence [Egypt Project filming], 1977 1981; Folder 5:1-5:2
      - correspondence [Egypt Tour], 1976 1980; Folder 5:3-5:4
      - correspondence [Father Elias Friedman], 1966 1982; Folder 5:5
      - correspondence [Giza Plateau mapping project], 1981 1987; Folder 5:6
      - correspondence [Zahi Hawass], 1976 1982; Folder 5:7
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] anonymous, 1974; Folder 5:8
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] A, 1977 1981; Folder 5:9
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] B, 1973 1982; Folder 5:10
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] Banks and Schellhorn, 1979 1982; Folder 5:11
    - Box 6
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] Colette Dutil, 1978 1982; Folder 6:1
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] D, 1975 1981; Folder 6:2
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] E, 1962 1980; Folder 6:3
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] F, 1977 1982; Folder 6:4
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] G, 1972 1983; Folder 6:5
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] H, 1976 1982; Folder 6:6
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] J-K, 1972 1982; Folder 6:7
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] L-M, 1963 1982; Folder 6:8
    - Box 6A
      - correspondence [Howard Metz], 1979 1981; Folder 6A:1
      - correspondence [Sharon Miles], 1976 1977; Folder 6A:2
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] N-R, 1976 1982; Folder 6A:3
      - correspondence [inquiries about archaeology] S-Z, 1971 1982; Folder 6A:4
      - correspondence [Mark Lehner], 1975 1977; Folder 6A:5-6A:8
    - Box 7
      - correspondence [Mark Lehner], 1978 1985; Folder 7:1-7:6
      - correspondence [Matthew McCauley], 1979; Folder 7:7
      - correspondence [John Mekarski], 1976; Folder 7:8-7:9
      - correspondence [Ahmed Mohamed Abdel Mawgoud], 1977; Folder 7:10
      - correspondence [Nag Hammadi dig], 1976 1979; Folder 7:11
      - correspondence [Arch Ogden], 1975; Folder 7:12
      - correspondence [Olga Esther Bazan Ordonez], 1978 1979; Folder 7:13
      - correspondence [Stanford Research Institute], 1975 1976; Folder 7:14
    - Box 8
      - correspondence [Stanford Research Institute], 1977 1981; Folder 8:1-8:2
      - correspondence [Timothy Welker], 1978; Folder 8:3
      - court documents, 1978; Folder 8:4
      - data [Egyptian archaeological projects], 1975 1985; Folder 8:5
      - interview [Mark Lehner], 1981; Folder 8:6
      - interview [Mark Lehner] by Edgar Evans Cayce and Robert Smith, 1985; Folder 8:7
      - interview [Mark Lehner and Robert Smith], 1992; Folder 8:8
      - journal [American Research Center in Egypt], 1979 1981; Folder 8:9-8:10
    - Box 9
      - journal [American Research Center in Egypt], 1986; Folder 9:1
      - journal [Israel Journey], 1977; Folder 9:2
      - journal [Journal of Egyptian Archaeology], 1985; Folder 9:3
      - magazine [Smithsonian], 1986; Folder 9:4
      - magazine [Travel and Leisure], 1977; Folder 9:5
      - magazine [Venture Inward], 1997; Folder 9:6
      - maps [Israel, topographical], 1978; Folder 9:7
      - newsclippings [Egypt Project], 1965 1982; Folder 9:8
      - newsletter [American Research Center in Egypt], 1979 1985; Folder 9:9-9:10
    - Box 10
      - newsletter [American Research Center in Egypt], 1984 1987; Folder 10:1
      - news releases [Egypt Project], 1976 1982; Folder 10:2
      - notes [Edgar Cayce Readings on Egypt], undated; Folder 10:3
      - notes [Egypt Project acoustics and drilling], 1974 1978; Folder 10:4
      - paper [Considerations Toward a Unified, Interdisciplinary, Cross-Cultural Epistemology] Mark Lehner, 1974; Folder 10:5
      - paper [Giza thesis] Mark Lehner, 1975; Folder 10:6
      - photographs [Egypt Project], 1978; Folder 10:7
      - photographs [Mount Carmel], 1977 1978; Folder 10:8
      - popular articles [Egyptian archaeology], 1974 1989; Folder 10:9
      - receipts [Egypt Project], 1978; Folder 10:10
      - report [Applications of Modern Sensing Techniques to Egyptology] Ain Sharma University and Stanford Research Institute, 1977; Folder 10:11
    - Box 11
      - report [The ARCE Sphinx Project: Proposal to the Edgar Cayce Foundation], 1982; Folder 11:1
      - reports [archaeological technology: Stanford Research Institute], 1977 1978; Folder 11:2
      - report [Edgar Cayce Foundation Egypt / Sphinx Research Project], 1976 1982; Folder 11:3
      - report draft materials [Edgar Cayce Foundation Egypt / Sphinx Project], 1982; Folder 11:4
      - report [Edgar Cayce Foundation Support of Archaeology in Egypt, A Review for E.C.F.], 1982; Folder 11:5
      - reports [Egypt Project], 1978 1982; Folder 11:6
      - reports [Egypt Project expense accounts], 1979 1982; Folder 11:7
      - report [Electromagnetic Sounder Experiments at the Pyramids of Giza] Ain Shams University and Stanford Research Institute, 1975; Folder 11:8
      - report [The Giza Plateau Mapping Project: Progress Report] Mark Lehner, 1984; Folder 11:9
      - report [Note on the Proposed Excavations at the Eastern Base of the Giza Plateau] Mark Lehner, undated; Folder 11:10
      - report [Report to the Edgar Cayce Foundation: Egypt 1973-1976] Mark Lehner, Folder 11:11
    - Box 12
      - report [Report to the Edgar Cayce Foundation: Egypt 1973-1976] Mark Lehner, Folder 12:1
      - report [The Sphinx Chronicle] Arch Ogden, 1978; Folder 12:2
      - report [Sphinx Project Taping Session], 1980; Folder 12:3; Tanous, Alex; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Jahoda, Joseph; Jahoda, Ursula; Jeffries, Robert; Jones, Scott; Jones, Johnnie
      - scholarly articles [Egyptian archaeology], 1961 1983; Folder 12:4
      - transcript [Karen Getsla and Mark Lehner at the Sphinx audio recording], 1976; Folder 12:5; Lehner, Mark; Getsla, Karen
      - travel materials [Egypt / Israel Tour], 1975 1979; Folder 12:6
      - report [Report on Psychic Information Relative to Essenes on Mt. Carmel; Prepared for the E.C.F.], 1977; Folder 12:7; Cayce, Hugh Lynn; Adriance, Robert; Dombrowski, Robert
  - Dreams, 1951 1979
    - Box 13
      - booklet [Our Judge and Jury] William N. Petersen, 1951 1961; Folder 13:1
      - correspondence [Dreams] A, 1968 1974; Folder 13:2
      - correspondence [Dreams] B, 1962 1979; Folder 13:3-13:6
      - correspondence [Dreams] C, 1961 1978; Folder 13:7
      - correspondence [Dreams] Deborah C. Clark, 1958 1963; Folder 13:8
      - correspondence [Dreams] D, 1963 1972; Folder 13:9
    - Box 14
      - correspondence [Dreams] E-F, 1962 1973; Folder 14:1
      - correspondence [Dreams] G, 1964 1979; Folder 14:2
      - correspondence [Dreams] H, 1961 1976; Folder 14:3
      - correspondence [Dreams] I-J, 1963 1971; Folder 14:4
      - correspondence [Dreams] K-L, 1960 1977; Folder 14:5
      - correspondence [Dreams] M-N, 1962 1973; Folder 14:6
      - correspondence [Dream Research Project] William McGarey, 1962 1963; Folder 14:7
      - correspondence [Dreams] O-P, 1958 1978; Folder 14:8
    - Box 15
      - correspondence [Dreams] R, 1962 1979; Folder 15:1
      - correspondence [Dreams] S, 1964 1975; Folder 15:2
      - correspondence [Dreams] T, 1964 1979; Folder 15:3
      - correspondence [Dreams] V, 1963 1971; Folder 15:4
      - correspondence [Dreams] W-Y, 1962 1971; Folder 15:5
      - newsclippings [Dreams], 1960 1970; Folder 15:6
      - notes [Dreams], 1964; Folder 15:7
      - notes [Dream Seminar], 1963 1964; Folder 15:8
      - publications [Dreams] A.R.E., 1951 1965; Folder 15:9
  - Doctors and Ministers, 1960 1980
    - Box 16
      - correspondence [Doctors] A-G, 1964 1980; Folder 16:1
      - correspondence [Doctors] H-W, 1963 1979; Folder 16:2
      - correspondence [Chiropractic Research Division, Edgar Cayce Foundation], 1968 1977; Folder 16:3-16:4
      - correspondence [Clinic staff], 1970 1977; Folder 16:5
      - correspondence [Robert Bradley], 1968 1973; Folder 16:6
      - correspondence [Robert Brewer], 1971 1974; Folder 16:7
      - correspondence [Charles Horton], 1961 1963; Folder 16:8
      - correspondence [Mayo Hotten], 1962 1975; Folder 16:9
      - correspondence [Lindsay Jacob], 1961 1980; Folder 16:10
      - correspondence [Richard Shames], 1976 1979; Folder 16:11
      - correspondence [Kenneth Starz], 1973 1975; Folder 16:12
      - correspondence [Thomas Tyndall], 1967 1974; Folder 16:13
    - Box 17
      - correspondence [Ministers], 1960 1980; Folder 17:1-17:3
      - correspondence [John Beams], 1968 1979; Folder 17:4
      - correspondence [Joseph Clower], 1973 2009; Folder 17:5
      - correspondence [George and Joelle Emery], 1966 1979; Folder 17:6
      - correspondence [First Presbyterian Church, Virginia Beach], 1963 1968; Folder 17:7
    - Box 17A
      - correspondence [First Presbyterian Church, Virginia Beach], 1969 1970; Folder 17A:1
      - correspondence [First Presbyterian Church, Virginia Beach] Sunday School, 1964 1966; Folder 17A:2
      - correspondence [Ralph Henard], 1965 1968; Folder 17A:3
      - correspondence [Presbyterian churchgoers], 1968 1978; Folder 17A:4
      - correspondence [Ralph Spears], 1970 1976; Folder 17A:5
      - correspondence [James Strange], 1979 1981; Folder 17A:6
      - correspondence [Tracy Walsh], 1963 1970; Folder 17A:7
  - Military, 1918 1945
    - Box 18
      - medal [Battle of Verdun], 1918; Item 18:1; Vernier, Seraphin Emile; metal, textile This medal was designed by artist Seraphin Vernier at the close of the First World War. It was given to anyone who served in the Argonne and St. Mihiel sectors between July 31, 1914 and November 11, 1918. The front depicts Marianne, the French symbol of victory. The reverse depicts the Porte Chaussee in the French city of Verdun.; 1.5 in W x 2.5 in H
      - medal [Deutschen Volksgemeinschaft badge], 1940 1945; Item 18:2; metal badge with pin fastener and enamel facing front: D.V.G. Westmark (LOTHR) reverse: W. Redo; Saarlautern; 0.75 in W x 0.75 in H
      - medal [German Iron Cross], 1939 1945; Item 18:3
      - patches [United States Army corporal chevrons], 1941 1945; Item 18:4
      - patches [United States Army sergeant rank], 1941 1945; Item 18:5
      - patch [United States Army European Theater of Operations Headquarters Communications], 1941 1945; Item 18:6
      - medal [United States Army good conduct], 1941 1945; Item 18:7
      - patch [United States Army honorable separation from service insignia], 1941 1945; Item 18:8
      - patch [United States 20th Army Corps], 1942 1945; Item 18:9
      - patch [United States Army 66th Infantry Division], 1943 1945; Item 18:10
      - medal [United States Army rifle marksmanship], 1941 1945; Item 18:11
      - patches [overseas service bars], 1941 1945; Item 18:12
      - medal [Winterschlacht im Osten], 1942; Item 18:13; The Eastern Medal, or the Winter Battle in the East Medal was given to any member of the Wehrmacht and Waffen-SS who served in the Eastern front between November 15, 1941 and April 15, 1942. It was also given posthumously to any German service member who died within the Soviet Union.
    - Box 19
      - booklet [Facing Life With God: A Spiritual Guide for Service Men and Women], 1943; Folder 19:1
      - correspondence [Horace Austin Jr.], 1945; Folder 19:2
      - correspondence [W.S. Bill Holloman], 1944; Folder 19:3
      - correspondence [Mary McTernan], 1944; Folder 19:4
      - correspondence [unidentified], 1944 1945; Folder 19:5
      - correspondence [Bill Weldon], 1946 1950; Folder 19:6
      - ephemera [France], 1942 1945; Folder 19:7
      - hypnosis suggestions, 1944; Folder 19:8
      - letters of recommendation for military service, 1943; Folder 19:9
      - photographs [Europe], 1942 1945; Folder 19:10
      - postcards, 1942 1945; Folder 19:11
      - typescript [Sunday Punch], 1944 1945; Folder 19:12-19:15
      - war department materials, 1942 1945; Folder 19:16
  - Personal, 1931 1982
    - Box 20
      - activity log [Boy Scout troop], 1931 1933; Folder 20:1
      - activity log [Boy Scout Western trip], 1934; Folder 20:2
      - correspondence [parents of Boy Scouts on cross-country trip], 1933; Folder 20:3
      - correspondence [personal], 1962 1981; Folder 20:4-20:6
      - manuscript [Roving Camp], undated; Folder 20:7-20:8
    - Box 21
      - photographs [Boy Scout scrapbook] copies, 1934; Folder 21:1
      - photograph album [Boy Scout Touring Camp 529], 1933; Folder 21:2
      - report [Second Trip West], 1934; Folder 21:3
      - scrapbook [Boy Scout Troop 60], 1937; Folder 21:4
    - Box 21A
      - notebook [dreams], 1937; Folder 21A:1
      - notes on dreams, 1955 1972; Folder 21A:2
      - dream journals (19), 1940 1981; Items 21A:3
    - Box 21B
      - boy scout materials, 1930 1940; Folder 21B:1
      - Boy Scouts of America literature, 1939 1956; Folder 21B:2
      - community service awards, 1964 1969; Folder 21B:3
      - correspondence [440], 1980; Folder 21B:4
      - correspondence [business], 1939 1982; Folder 21B:5
      - correspondence [Annie Cayce], 1945; Folder 21B:6
      - correspondence [Edgar and Gertrude Cayce], 1927; Folder 21B:6a
      - correspondence [Edgar Evans Cayce], 1945; Folder 21B:7
      - correspondence [Sally Taylor Cayce], 1944 1945; Folder 21B:8
      - correspondence [health concerns], 1976 1981; Folder 21B:9
      - correspondence [Sarah Cayce Hesson], 1976 1978; Folder 21B:10
      - correspondence [personal], 1930 1980; undated; Folder 21B:11
      - correspondence [White Horse Hill treasure], 1974 1976; Folder 21B:12
      - diary [A.R.E. China Tour], 1981-08-20 1981-09-13; Folder 21B:13
      - essay [Let's Go Camping], undated; Folder 21B:14
      - minutes [Church of the Redeemer Chapter Brotherhood of St. Andrew], 1944 1948; Folder 21B:18
      - minutes [First Presbyterian Church committee], 1966 1970; Folder 21B:19
      - proposal [Memorial Project for Hugh Lynn Cayce] Cayce-Reilly Health Center, 1983; Folder 21B:20
      - report cards, 1916 1924; Folder 21B:21
      - report [United Presbyterian Church U.S.A. Task Force on Psychic and Occult Activities], 1975; Folder 21B:22
      - essays [Washington and Lee University], 1929 1930; Folder 21B:15
      - magazines [esoteric], 1961 1966; Folder 21B:16
      - identification documentation, 1950 1980; Folder 21B:17
    - Box 21C
      - binder #1 [audio cassettes and transcripts] transcribed by Ken Wight, 1997; Folder 21C:1
      - binder #2 [audio cassettes and transcripts] transcribed by Ken Wight, 1997; Folder 21C:2
      - binder #3 [audio cassettes and transcripts] transcribed by Ken Wight, 1997; Folder 21C:3
      - binder #4 [audio cassettes and transcripts] transcribed by Ken Wight, 1997; Folder 21C:4
      - binder #5 [audio cassettes and transcripts] transcribed by Ken Wight, 1997; Folder 21C:5
      - correspondence [Larry King interview with Hugh Lynn Cayce], 1980; Folder 21C:6
      - song [His Name was Edgar Cayce] John Pagano, undated; Folder 21C:7
      - transcript, class [Highlights from the Edgar Cayce Work Readings [Robert Adriance], undated; Folder 21C:8
      - transcript, class [Karma] Irene Hickman; Asilomar, 1970; Folder 21C:9
      - transcript, class [William McGarey], undated; Folder 21C:10
      - transcript, class [Meditation] Helen Ruth Schroeder, 1971; Folder 21C:11
      - transcript, class [Steps to Cosmic Awareness] Maynor Bates, 1970; Folder 21C:12
      - transcript, class [The Soul and the Biological Machine] Daniel Rosewood, undated; Folder 21C:13
      - transcript, class [untitled; Asilomar] Nancy Whitman, 1971; Folder 21C:14
      - transcript, interview [Tom Baugh; Lena Wicks; Mrs. D.C. Wright], undated; Folder 21C:15
      - transcript, interview [Hugh Lynn Cayce] by A. Robert Smith, 1981; Folder 21C:16
      - transcript, interview [Hugh Lynn Cayce] The Edgar Cayce Legacy, undated; Folder 21C:17
      - transcript, interview [Vernon Herbert; member of Hugh Lynn Cayce's Boy Scout troop] by Jeanette Thomas, 1994; Folder 21C:18
      - transcript, interview [Wesley and Velma Ketchum], 1962; Folder 21C:19
      - transcripts, interviews [parapsychology; conducted by Weeks Parker], 1964 1968; Folder 21C:20
      - transcript, interview [Damion Simpson], undated; Folder 21C:21
      - transcript, lecture [Baptism of Love] Starr Daily, undated; Folder 21C:22
      - transcript, lecture [Creation Study Groups] Fay Batts, undated; Folder 21C:23
      - transcript, lecture [Habits, Hobbies, and Happiness] Mae St. Clair, undated; Folder 21C:24
      - transcript, lecture [Inner Light Foundation] Betty Bethards, 1971; Folder 21C:25
      - transcript, lecture [The Edgar Cayce Story] Hugh Lynn Cayce, undated; Folder 21C:26
      - transcript, lecture [The Way of Holy Affection] Starr Daily, undated; Folder 21C:27
      - transcript, lecture [untitled] Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1971; Folder 21C:28
      - transcript, lecture [Preparation for ESP] Mae St. Clair, undated; Folder 21C:29
      - transcript, lecture [Where Are We Going?] Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1972; Folder 21C:30
      - transcripts, letters [family members], undated; Folder 21C:31
      - transcript [psychic reading] Byron Pace, 1965; Folder 21C:32
      - transcript [psychic reading for Raymond J. Liebling] Grace Wittenberger, 1967; Folder 21C:33
      - announcements [radio programs] Hugh Lynn Cayce, 1967 1970; Folder 21C:34